http://www.rochestercathedral.org/privacy-policy

Safeguarding
Worship & Music/Worship onlineServicesMusicBaptism, Confirmation & Holy CommunionWeddingsFunerals
Visit/Visiting informationCovid-19 FAQGroup visitsPilgrimageCafé in the CryptShopVisit RochesterFilmingAnnual Report and Accounts
Learning/Schools, colleges and universitiesFamily activitiesThe LibraryA brief historyTextus Roffensis: Rochester's Mystery BookRochester Cathedral Research GuildVirtual TourVirtual Cathedral Project
What's on/News
Cathedral Trust/
Get Involved/FriendsBusiness GuildDonate onlineOur Fundraising PromiseBeaconCommunitySunday ClubWork with usVolunteer
Venue Hire/
Contact/
Safeguarding/
Privacy Policy
Worship & Music/Worship onlineServicesMusicBaptism, Confirmation & Holy CommunionWeddingsFunerals
Visit/Visiting informationCovid-19 FAQGroup visitsPilgrimageCafé in the CryptShopVisit RochesterFilmingAnnual Report and Accounts
Learning/Schools, colleges and universitiesFamily activitiesThe LibraryA brief historyTextus Roffensis: Rochester's Mystery BookRochester Cathedral Research GuildVirtual TourVirtual Cathedral Project
What's on/News
Cathedral Trust/
Get Involved/FriendsBusiness GuildDonate onlineOur Fundraising PromiseBeaconCommunitySunday ClubWork with usVolunteer
Venue Hire/
Contact/
Safeguarding/
Privacy policyIn accordance with data protection legislation, Rochester Cathedral is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information of visitors using this Site.What and when we collectWe may collect personal information such as your name, contact information, credit card information and demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests (the “Personal Data”). Your Personal Data is collected when you contact us, request information, make a booking, purchase items (including etickets) or support us. Note that the credit card information you give for any online transaction via our secure webpage is used solely for the purpose of processing that transaction.Consent to collect your Personal Data and what we do with itYou hereby agree that your Personal Data may be collected and processed by us (and stored by our designated data collection agency) for the following purposes:processing your requests;providing you with our newsletter and other information by email or other means;providing you with information about our products and services or those of other parties we think you may find interesting;providing a personalised service;maintaining accounts and records;statistical analysis and conducting market research surveys;assessing and evaluating the use that is being made of the Site;information and databank compilation and administration.We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
Worship & Music/Worship onlineServicesMusicBaptism, Confirmation & Holy CommunionWeddingsFunerals
Visit/Visiting informationCovid-19 FAQGroup visitsPilgrimageCafé in the CryptShopVisit RochesterFilmingAnnual Report and Accounts
Learning/Schools, colleges and universitiesFamily activitiesThe LibraryA brief historyTextus Roffensis: Rochester's Mystery BookRochester Cathedral Research GuildVirtual TourVirtual Cathedral Project
What's on/News
Cathedral Trust/
Get Involved/FriendsBusiness GuildDonate onlineOur Fundraising PromiseBeaconCommunitySunday ClubWork with usVolunteer
Venue Hire/
Contact/
Safeguarding/
Rochester Cathedral
Rochester Cathedral – a place of Christian worship since AD604. Located in the heart of Rochester on the banks of the River Medway in Kent.
Closure notices
Areas of the Cathedral that remain closed are:
The Crypt: café, shop and exhibition; Library, South Door and toilets. Appointments can be made by email to visit the Garth.The Lady Chapel is now open.We continue to react to the ongoing changes to government guidelines as they are published.
Friday 9th and Monday 12th October
Scaffolding worksThe Nave will be closed. Access to Quire only, via North Door.
Subscribe to our newsletter
for the latest news and events at Rochester Cathedral
Email Address
Sign Up
We respect your privacy.
Thank you!
Rochester CathedralThe Chapter OfficeGarth House, The PrecinctRochesterKent, ME1 1SXTelephone 01634 843366Email info@rochestercathedral.org
Articles RSS
Cathedral opening hours: Please see home page for detailsCathedral ClosuresServicesHow to find usContactVenue HireFAQPress and Media informationLegal NoticePrivacy PolicyCathedral PoliciesSafeguardingAnti-bullying & Harassment PolicyWhistleblowing
Diocese of Rochester
Site created by Olley DesignPhotography by Clive Tanner
